Rebecca Mi-Ja Kang

021 0908 6245 • happykang@gmail.com • Auckland

PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Organized and reliable worker with about 2 years of experience specialty in a food factory. Possessing a commercial head, as well as exceptional cooking skills allows her keep a kitchen effective and operational no matter how busy it gets. Looking to obtain a full-time position within the areas of expertise.

EDUCATION

Mar 2006- Aug 2011: Bachelor of Educational Science Korea National Open Univ. South Korea

• Majored in Early Childhood Education

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2020–Present: KATSUBI HQ Co., Ltd Auckland Staff

Responsible for carrying out a wide range of duties to produce frozen foods at HQ factory

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Loaded materials and products into package processing equipment.
- Printing and attaching labels for each products
- Wrapping frozen foods to be delivered to branches
- Cleaning and arranging the cold storage
- Entering recipes and ingredients into spreadsheets.
- Disposing of rubbish and waste

May 2018–Aug 2018: Galley Cafe Auckland Kitchen hand

Responsible for carrying out a wide range of duties in a busy kitchen environment.

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Making sure that the chef has everything they need to carry out their duties
- Assisting the Kitchen Manager in food prepping, cooking and cleaning
- Washing up dishes and kitchen utensils
- Disposing of rubbish and waste
- Setting up the kitchen service counter
- Mopping up any spills immediately

Sep 2016-Feb 2017: Solmaroo Kindergarten S.Korea Assistant Teacher

- Collaborated with lead teachers to help children reach their goals.
- Assisted with small and large group activities, as well as preparation of materials and learning spaces.

 Developed and led learning activities on field days and other special event days, including Week of the Young Child

Sep 2012-Oct 2013: Ha-im Kindergarten S.Korea Assistant Teacher

- Collaborated with lead teachers to help children reach their goals.
- Assisted with small and large group activities, as well as preparation of materials and learning spaces.
- Developed and led learning activities on field days and other special event days, including Week of the Young Child

Mar 2012–Sep 2012: Boddle Kindergarten S.Korea Assistant Teacher

- Collaborated with lead teachers to help children reach their goals.
- Assisted with small and large group activities, as well as preparation of materials and learning spaces.
- Developed and led learning activities on field days and other special event days, including Week of the Young Child

PRESONAL INTERESTS/ACTIVITIES

- A very calm and polite person who enjoys swinning and running
- Member of Auckland Tabernacle Baptist Church

OTHER

Open Work Visa (Exp. 14/10/2024) New Zealand Driver Licence: Full